<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BloodDonationBuddy</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">MAD305 Project</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">w0806279@myscc.ca</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--Navigation Drawer Titles-->
    <string name="menu_home">Welcome</string>
    <string name="menu_learn">Blood Types</string>
    <string name="menu_process">Donation Process</string>
    <string name="menu_eligibility">Can You Donate?</string>
    <string name="menu_credits">Credits</string>

    <!--WelcomePage content-->
    <string name="welcomePageTitle">Welcome to the Blood Donation Buddy App!</string>
    <string name="welcomePageImgDesc">An infographic showing the makeup of blood and listing the blood types/</string>
    <string name="welcomePageContent">Welcome to the BloodDonationBuddy App! This app serves a purpose to provide information about the blood donation process.
        It will detail what blood donation is and why it is a great act of kindness.
        You will also be able to learn about the various different blood types to learn what it tells about you,
        and what the blood donation process looks like.
        It even allows you to determine whether or not you can donate blood by asking some simple questions about yourself.
    </string>

    <!--Learn BloodTypes Page Content-->
    <string name="typeA">TYPE A BLOOD</string>
    <string name="typeB">TYPE B BLOOD</string>
    <string name="typeAB">TYPE AB BLOOD</string>
    <string name="typeO">TYPE O BLOOD</string>
    <string name="typeError">ERROR</string>
    <string-array name="bloodTypes">
        <item>@string/typeA</item>
        <item>@string/typeB</item>
        <item>@string/typeAB</item>
        <item>@string/typeO</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="typeAContent">Type A blood is the first of the four main blood groups. It consists of A+ and A- blood,
    both of which are determined by the presence of a protein molecule called the Rh factor. This is a protein that aids with the bodies
    natural defense and antibodies. This blood type group makes up almost 40% of the US population, with 33% being A+ and 7% being A-, according to
    the CleavlandClinic. The A in this blood group comes from the fact that the blood has the presence of the A blood antigen, which determines the A
    group designation. In general being part of the Type A blood group puts you in a common group with a large proportion of the population.</string>
    <string name="typeBContent">Type B blood is the second of the four main blood groups. There are again 2 groups for the blood group, which are
    B+ and B-, which are again determined by the presence/lack of the Rh factor protein. The B blood type is considerably less common than the A group,
    with roughly 11% of the US population being part of this group. This makes this group one of the less common blood types to have, and therefore
    the donation/reception of this blood group varies from group A, and there are a lot fewer donors for this blood type.</string>
    <string name="typeABContent">Type AB blood is the third major blood group. It means that a person has both A and B blood antigens, and therefore they are a combination
    of type A and B, and therefore make up the AB group. This is very uncommon among the general population, with only around 5% of the US population being part
    of this group. In fact, AB- is the least common blood type in the US, with under 1% of the population having this blood type. This makes an AB blood type person
    extremely rare and reflects there donation/reception status.</string>
    <string name="typeOContent">Finally there is the fourth main blood group - Type O. This is different then the A and B types that make up the first 3 groups.
        This blood type designation means that a persons blood does not have A or B blood antigens. Therefore they fall into a different classification called O.
        The Type O group is interestingly very polar in its breakdown among the general population. O+ is actually the most common blood type in the US with almost 40%
        having this blood type, and on the other end only about 7% are O-. This is a large difference that constitutes different reception and donation eligibility for
        people with type O blood.
    </string>

    <!--Donation Process Page Content-->
    <string name="donationTitle">Typical Blood Donation Process</string>

    <string name="arrive">Arrive to Donation Center</string>
    <string name="checkup">Complete Checkup and Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate Blood</string>
    <string name="refreshments">Enjoy Refreshments</string>
    <string name="satisfaction">Rejoice!</string>

    <string name="arriveDesc">When you arrive to the donation center you are expected to have had a meal prior to coming and have
    had sufficient fluids in the hours leading up to your donation. This is because your blood needs to be viscous in order
    to be drawn easily for a smooth experience. Upon arrival to the donation center you will have to present ID and check-in
    with the staff. This will then lead to you answering a questionnaire with questions about your self and then a staff member
    will verify the information and allow you to continue to the next step of the process.</string>
    <string name="checkupDesc">You are then given a quick checkup to verify you are in good shape and well in order to give blood.
    A quick prick from your finger to test your hemoglobin levels may be done in order to ensure your blood is in adequate shape for
    donation. You will then be brought to the donation room and the donation process will begin soon after.</string>
    <string name="donateDesc">You will be seated into a reclined chair and will be asked which arm you prefer to donate from.
    You will then be briefed on how long the process will take and any potential problems you could have. A typical donation
    yield is 450-500ml of blood, which is only about 10% of the blood flowing in your body. The area on your arm is sterilized
    and the needle is passed into your vein. From here it takes about 15 minutes tops for the blood to full the vile, and as its happening
    staff will be watching to make sure you are feeling OK. It is recommended to talk and keep alert to ensure an enjoyable
    experience. Once your done your insertion point is cleaned and bandaged, and you are given a final report of your donation.</string>
    <string name="refreshmentDesc">This may be the best part of whole process - the snacks! There are usually snacks and refreshments
    for downers after they are done, like cookies, chips,etc. Enjoy these snacks as a token of appreciation for your generosity
    and altruism - you deserved them!</string>
    <string name="satisfactionDesc">That was all! Congratulations on completing a blood donation. This is something that
    not everyone does, but for the ones that do its one of the greatest gifts they could give. You are providing a lifeline
    for a stranger that could save their life and all it takes is around an hour from start to end. You can donate blood multiple
    times a year if you would like, and once you have donated once you can have a donor ID that makes your donation process
    that much simpler. Giving the gift of life is perhaps the greatest gift of all, and you did just that!</string>

    <!--Donation Process Page Content-->
    <string name="formTitle">Determine Donation Eligibility</string>
    <string name="ageLabel">How old are you?</string>
    <string name="tattooLabel">Have you had tattoos in the past 3 months?</string>
    <string name="dentalLabel">Have you had a dental operation in the last 3 days?</string>
    <string name="pregnantLabel">Are you currently pregnant or have delivered in the past 6 months?</string>
    <string name="weightLabel">Do you weigh more than 110 lbs?</string>
    <string name="medicineLabel">Are you taking prescription medication?</string>
    <string name="eligibleButton">Check Eligibility</string>

    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>


    <string-array name="ageOptions">
        <item>12–17</item>
        <item>18–25</item>
        <item>26–39</item>
        <item>40–65</item>
        <item>65+</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="eligible">YOU ARE ELIGIBLE TO DONATE BLOOD!</string>
    <string name="notEligible">YOU AREN\'T ELIGIBLE TO DONATE BLOOD!</string>
    <string name="ageProblem">YOU ARE NOT 18 YEARS OLD YET!</string>
    <string name="tattooProblem">YOU CAN\'T HAVE TATTOOS LESS THAN 3 MONTHS OLD!</string>
    <string name="dentalProblem">YOU CAN\'T DONATE UNTIL 3 DAYS AFTER!</string>
    <string name="weightProblem">YOU NEED TO BE AT LEAST 110LBS</string>
    <string name="pregnantProblem">YOU CAN\'T HAVE BEEN PREGNANT OR DELIVERED IN THE PAST 6 MONTHS!</string>
    <string name="medicineProblem">YOU MUST VERIFY YOUR MEDICATION DOES NOT INFRINGE DONATION ABILITY!!</string>


    <!--Donation History Page Content-->
    <string name="yearOne">1628</string>
    <string name="yearTwo">1665</string>
    <string name="yearThree">1667</string>
    <string name="yearFour">1795</string>
    <string name="yearFive">1840</string>
    <string name="yearSix">1884</string>
    <string name="yearSeven">1900</string>
    <string name="yearEight">1907</string>
    <string name="yearNine">1912</string>
    <string name="yearTen">1932</string>
    <string name="yearEleven">1940</string>
    <string name="yearTwelve">1947</string>
    <string name="yearThirteen">1950</string>
    <string name="yearFourteen">1951</string>
    <string name="yearFifteen">1961</string>
    <string name="yearSixteen">1970</string>
    <string name="yearSeventeen">1983</string>
    <string name="yearEighteen">1992</string>
    <string name="yearNineteen">2002</string>
    <string name="yearNTwenty">2003</string>
    <string name="yearTwentyOne">2018</string>

    <string name="eventOne">Discovery of blood circulation by William Harvey.</string>
    <string name="eventTwo">First successful blood transfusion in England by Richard Lower.</string>
    <string name="eventThree">Successful sheep-to-human transfusions reported in France and England.</string>
    <string name="eventFour">Philip Syng Physick performs the first human blood transfusion in Philadelphia.</string>
    <string name="eventFive">Samuel Armstrong Lane performs the first successful whole blood transfusion in London.</string>
    <string name="eventSix">Saline infusion replaces milk as a "blood substitute."</string>
    <string name="eventSeven">Karl Landsteiner discovers the first three human blood groups.</string>
    <string name="eventEight">Ludvig Hektoen suggests cross-matching blood for safer transfusions.</string>
    <string name="eventNine">Roger Lee and Paul Dudley White coin the terms "universal donor" and "universal recipient." after
    learning that type O blood can be given to any patient, and AB types can receive any type</string>
    <string name="eventTen">Establishment of the first blood bank in Leningrad.</string>
    <string name="eventEleven">US government establishes a blood collection program for the UK during WW2.</string>
    <string name="eventTwelve">ABO blood-typing and syphilis testing on each blood unit.</string>
    <string name="eventThirteen">Introduction of plastic bags for blood collection by Carl Walter and W.P. Murphy, Jr.</string>
    <string name="eventFourteen">Formation of the American Association of Blood Banks committee on Inspection and Accreditation.</string>
    <string name="eventFifteen">Recognition of platelet concentrates for reducing mortality in cancer patients.</string>
    <string name="eventSixteen">Shift toward an all-volunteer blood donor system in US blood banks.</string>
    <string name="eventSeventeen">Additive solutions extend red blood cell shelf life to 42 days.</string>
    <string name="eventEighteen">Implementation of HIV-1 and HIV-2 testing for donor blood.</string>
    <string name="eventNineteen">Identification of West Nile virus as transfusion transmissible.</string>
    <string name="eventNTwenty">FDA licensing of Nucleic acid amplification test (NAT) for HIV and HCV.</string>
    <string name="eventTwentyOne">FDA grants emergency use authorization for freeze-dried plasma in combat settings.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>